<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>List of all info pages on IR Anthology</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/</link><description>Recent content in List of all info pages on IR Anthology</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Information for Submitters</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/contrib/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/contrib/</guid><description>This page contains general information about submitting the proceedings of a conference to the ACL Anthology. (For information about the complete conference management process, particularly for ACL conference publications chairs, please refer to the official documentation.) It is intended for publication chairs of main conferences and standalone events, who have the responsibility of delivering the proceedings for all main conference and workshop volumes to the Anthology director. Chairs of workshops attached to a larger conference should also read this page, but should work through their main conference publication chair instead of directly with the Anthology.</description></item><item><title>Requesting Corrections</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/corrections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/corrections/</guid><description>Types of corrections The staff of the ACL Anthology can process requests for both many types of corrections to data in the ACL Anthology. These include correcting metadata and posting errata and revisions for scholarly works that are already published. While this service can help correct post-publication problems, due to certain difficulties and liabilities, the corrections have certain limitations, which we describe here.
Corrections to metadata do not require the submission of a new PDF.</description></item><item><title>Anthology development and API</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/development/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/development/</guid><description>API All Anthology data is stored under the data directory. In the xml directory are the files that contain all the Anthology metadata, in a format described below. The yaml directory contains various other important information.
In addition, we have a Python API that defines objects for papers, authors, volumes, and so on. This is all accessible by an Anthology object that can be access in the following manner. First, clone the Anthology Github repo and setup your environment:</description></item><item><title>Anthology Identifiers</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/ids/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/ids/</guid><description>Every item in the anthology is assigned an Anthology ID and a canonical URL so that they can be easily located and referenced.
Identifier format We introduced a new identifier scheme in 2020 in order to accommodate growth in the Anthology. Everything ingested in 2020 and afterwards will have these IDs (including volumes from years prior to 2020). The new identifiers are of the form YEAR.VENUE-VOLUME.NUMBER, where
YEAR is the 4-digit year (e.</description></item><item><title>Twenty More Years of Computational Linguistics</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/reflections-aj/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/reflections-aj/</guid><description>The title can be read in two ways. Either I should comment on the past twenty years of ACL (which coincide with the period between ACL 1982 held at Penn and ACL 2002 also held at Penn) or twenty more years from ACL 2002. As you will see many of my comments will be relevant to both these interpretations.
How did I get into computational linguistics (CL)? I did not really get into it.</description></item><item><title>ACL 1993—1994</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/reflections-ksj/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/reflections-ksj/</guid><description>As an organisation, the ACL has clearly evolved over the forty years since its foundation. (Whether, or how, it has evolved in its area of intellectual interest over the same period is a tricky and interesting question.) The ACL&amp;rsquo;s organisational development in the period up to Don Walker&amp;rsquo;s death in 1993 was, however, rather different from its evolution since. This was partly because the ACL&amp;rsquo;s community was not very large in its first two decades, partly because there were only three Secretary-Treasurers in the whole period from 1963 to 1993.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/credits/</guid><description>The IR Anthology is a grassroots initative run entirely by contributions from volunteers.
Active Volunteers Janek Bevendorff (Bauhaus-Universität Weimar) Jan Philipp Bittner (Martin-Luther-Universität Halle-Wittenberg) Alexander Bondarenko (Martin-Luther-Universität Halle-Wittenberg) Maik Fröbe (Martin-Luther-Universität Halle-Wittenberg) Sebastian Günther (Martin-Luther-Universität Halle-Wittenberg) Christian Kahmann (Leipzig University) Andreas Niekler (Leipzig University) Michael Völske (Bauhaus-Universität Weimar) Directors Martin Potthast (Leipzig University) Matthias Hagen (Martin-Luther-Universität Halle-Wittenberg) Benno Stein (Bauhaus-Universität Weimar) Donors Contributions from the IR community and beyond are welcome.</description></item><item><title>Help Shape the ACL Anthology!</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/volunteer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/info/volunteer/</guid><description>The ACL Anthology is a treasure. It is the repository of our community&amp;rsquo;s scientific contributions extending back over fifty years; its engine is nicely designed custom in-house software that still works well after almost two decades; and it has enabled research projects examining topics like author networks and topic shift over time. That all of this labor has been donated by its members further distinguishes the Anthology: it is not a found treasure, but one that has been crafted and shaped over countless hours, as if by a hundred Berninis, holding keyboards instead of chisels.</description></item></channel></rss>