<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frequently Asked Questions on IR Anthology</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/</link><description>Recent content in Frequently Asked Questions on IR Anthology</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How can I make suggestions or provide feedback on the Anthology?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/feedback/</guid><description>We welcome your feedback! The most convenient way for us to receive it is for you to create a new issue on our Github issues page, or to add a new comment to our feedback mega-thread. If you prefer, you are also invited to email the Anthology director.</description></item><item><title>How can I submit corrections to papers?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/corrections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/corrections/</guid><description>Please read the information on our corrections page.</description></item><item><title>How do I link to publications in the ACL Anthology?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/linking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/linking/</guid><description>Every paper in the Anthology is assigned an Anthology ID. After 2020, identifiers are of the form {year}.{venue}-{volume}.{#}, where {year} is the four-digit year, {venue} a lowercased venue code comprising ASCII letters and digits, {volume} is a volume name or number, and {#} is the paper number. Prior to 2020, this identifier took the form CYY-VPPP or CYY-VVPP, where C is a collection, YY a two-digit year, V a volume, and P a paper ID.</description></item><item><title>How can I submit attachments to papers?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/attachments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/attachments/</guid><description>To submit paper attachments, use this Microsoft form. Important: If the file attachment cannot be downloaded automatically (via wget), processing of your attachment will fail. Many sharing sites (Github, Google Drive, Dropbox) display by default an HTML page. This complicates processing of attachments and increases the time it takes. Please manually check that you can download your file via wget.
Attachments are processed at least quarterly, at the beginning of January, April, July, and October.</description></item><item><title>How can I submit my proceedings or journal to the Anthology?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/submitting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/submitting/</guid><description>Please see our submission guide.</description></item><item><title>How does the ACL Anthology use Digital Object Identifiers (DOIs)?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/doi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/doi/</guid><description>The ACL uses DOIs to refer to scholarly works persistently in accordance with cross-disciplinary standards. Prior to 2012, ACL materials were assigned DOIs by the Association of Computational Machinery (ACM). Since 2014, ACL has assigned its own DOIs to materials using a convention based off of the ACL Anthology Identifiers. In 2015, ACL had to change DOI prefix due to accounting practices for the ACM.
Prefixes:
2014&amp;ndash;2015: 10.3115 2015&amp;ndash;current: 10.18653 We strongly encourage the publication of DOIs in citing bibliographies to help better cross-reference ACL materials.</description></item><item><title>What is the copyright for materials in the ACL Anthology?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/copyright/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/copyright/</guid><description>The ACL materials that are hosted in the Anthology are licensed to the general public under a liberal usage policy that allows unlimited reproduction, distribution and hosting of materials on any other website or medium, for non-commercial purposes. Prior to 2016, all ACL materials are licensed using the Creative Commons 3.0 BY-NC-SA (Attribution, Non-Commercial, Share-Alike) license. As of 2016, this policy has been relaxed further, and all subsequent materials are available to the general public on the terms of the Creative Commons 4.</description></item><item><title>How can I help improve the ACL Anthology?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/volunteer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/volunteer/</guid><description>We welcome your contributions! In fact, since the Anthology is run entirely on volunteer energy, we need them. The best way to contribute is to browse our Github issues page (we suggest starting with the &amp;ldquo;help wanted&amp;rdquo; tag, and see what needs to be done that overlaps with your interests or skills. Please also feel free to email the director, anthology@aclweb.org. You might also be interested in our call for volunteers.</description></item><item><title>What other resources are there based on the ACL Anthology?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/related-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/related-work/</guid><description>The ACL Anthology Reference Corpus provides plain text and other metadata for a controlled subset of the ACL Anthology.
The following people have written reflections on the ACL Anthology:
Aravind Joshi Karen Spärck Jones A 2018 paper gave a technical description of the Anthology at the time:
The ACL Anthology: Current State and Future Directions Daniel Gildea, Min-Yen Kan, Nitin Madnani, Christoph Teichmann, Martin Villalba Proceedings of Workshop for NLP Open Source Software (NLP-OSS)</description></item><item><title>What software does the ACL Anthology use?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/software/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/software/</guid><description>The ACL Anthology is built using completely open-source software, with further developments and customization done by the ACL Anthology staff. The current Anthology website is statically generated using the Hugo framework, with the layout being designed using the Bootstrap library. Font Awesome is used as the icon font.
The source code for the Anthology is available on GitHub at https://github.com/acl-org/acl-anthology/.</description></item><item><title>How can I programmatically access the Anthology's data?</title><link>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ir.webis.de/anthology/faq/api/</guid><description>Please see our developer documentation.</description></item></channel></rss>